affspy.com 2010-10-25

# Affspy :: #1 Affiliate Intelligence Tool

## Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the AffSpy.com website, (hereinafter referred to as “the Site” or “AffSpy.com”), which is owned by AffSpy, Inc., a Delaware corporation (hereinafter referred to as “AffSpy,” “us,” or “we”), and reviewing our Privacy Policy, effective February 28, 2008. AffSpy is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our many offerings. 

### Overview

This Privacy Policy (hereinafter “Policy”) governs your use of AffSpy.com. This Policy describes much of the information that we collect from you and what may happen to that information. For example, this Policy is intended to let you know about information we collect from you; what cookies are and how they may be used; how your information is often used; who is collecting your information; with whom your information may be shared; what options are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information; how you may use other users’ information; the types of security precautions in place to protect against loss, misuse, or alteration of your information; how AffSpy protects children’s privacy; and other important information about your online privacy. 

Please note that we review our privacy practices from time to time, and that our practices are subject to change. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Policy. All amended terms shall be automatically effective after they are posted on the Site and applied retroactively if you use this Site after this Policy is amended.

By visiting the Site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Site. 

### What Personally Identifiable Information does AffSpy collect?

A primary purpose of collecting information from you is to provide you with a safe, smooth, effective, and personalized experience. We will only collect information about you that we consider necessary. 

Generally, AffSpy collects information in several ways. Some information is gathered if you register. This includes, but is not limited to, your email address and password. You may also choose to submit optional information, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and website address. We often indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. Additionally, we save browsing and data log information linked to your account. We also collect personal information when you report a problem, either through the Site’s contact form or email system. We may also collect information that you post on our blog or that you return to us through feedback forms or surveys. If you contact AffSpy, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

Wherever AffSpy collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page. 

### What are “cookies” and how does AffSpy use them?

Data collection devices, such as “cookies,” are used to store, and sometimes track, information about you. Generally, these cookies help provide personalized services and promote trust and safety. A cookie is a small file containing a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and placed on your computer’s hard drive to assist us in providing our services. All pages on the Site where you are prompted to login or that are customizable may require that you accept cookies. Our cookies are only read by the server that placed them and are unable to execute any code or virus. More specifically, we may use cookies to:

(1) Remind us of who you are when you login and to access your account information in order to deliver to you a more personalized service;  
(2) Allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session;  
(3) Measure your visiting and purchasing/affiliate patterns in the aggregate. Aggregate data (data gathered across all user accounts) may be gathered in a non-personally identifiable form to build higher quality online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our visitors, such as how long and how often users view certain pages;  
(4) Determine your clickstream to the Site;  
(5) Better personalize the content that you and other users will see on the Site;  
(6) Collect IP addresses and log-in information for system administration;   
(7) Automatically share some information with Google Analytics to analyze a broad range of information. However, the analytics are exclusively for our internal use to better manage the website experience for our visitors and evaluate advertising strategies and tactics (no personally identifiable information is shared with Google); and  
(8) Other purposes to assist us in delivering the highest quality service possible.

You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits.

### How does AffSpy use my information?

AffSpy uses your information to provide you with a customized browsing experience. We also may use your personal information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, respond to your inquiries, detect and protect against error, fraud, or other criminal activity, enforce our User Agreement, and for any other purposes that AffSpy deems appropriate.

In order to provide services free of charge, we display advertisements. The advertiser never has access to individual account information. Only AffSpy has access to individuals’ accounts. By accepting the User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you expressly agree to receive these advertisements.

### Who is collecting information?

When you are using the Site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information with AffSpy. You acknowledge that data can be collected, maintained by, or transferred to a company other than AffSpy.

Please be advised that AffSpy advertisers or websites that have links on the Site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those web sites linked to AffSpy.com are not covered by this Policy.

### With whom does AffSpy.com share my information?

AffSpy will not disclose your personally identifiable information except as described below: 

_Blog/Forums_

: If you post on our blog, forum, or chat room, some personally identifiable information may be seen by other members or users. This includes, but is not limited to, the poster’s name, date of post, comments, IP address, and other information. 

_AffSpy Employees and Contractors_

: Some of our employees and contractors are subject to non-disclosure agreements with us. These and other legal restrictions prohibit their use of the information you provide us for any purpose except to facilitate the specific AffSpy-related operation, unless you explicitly agreed or gave your prior permission to them for additional uses. 

_Advertisers_

: If you complete a transaction with an advertiser linked to AffSpy, the information obtained during your visit to that advertiser, and the information you give, may be provided to the advertiser. Advertisers linked to the Site have separate policy practices for which AffSpy has no responsibility or liability.

We may disclose account information where we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating AffSpy’s policies as specified in the Privacy Policy or User Agreement, violating state or federal law, or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) AffSpy’s rights or property, other users of the Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. AffSpy may disclose or access account information when we believe that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain and improve our services.

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they unlawfully collect from the Site. We will try to protect your privacy, however, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

### What are my choices regarding collection, use, and distribution of my information?

AffSpy will contact you (by email, phone, and/or mail) if you complete a contact form on the Site, if you sign up for a membership, or if you contact us directly by direct mail or email. We will also contact you regarding any problems with your account and for website misuse. We may also contact you regarding our services, such as new features regarding the Site. If you do not wish to receive optional communications, simply update your membership profile.

### How may I use other users’ information?

Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all applicable local laws and rules regarding online conduct and privacy, as well as content. Specifically, but not as a limitation, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding transmission of technical and personal data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.

 _Spam_

. We do not tolerate spam. You are not licensed to add us or any registered user to your mail (email or physical mail) list without his or her affirmative consent. You are not licensed to use spam in promoting AffSpy.com. 

### What security precautions are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of my information?

Whenever AffSpy handles your personal information, we take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant User Agreement and this Policy. Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We use procedural and mechanical safeguards to protect your personal information against loss or theft as well as unauthorized access and disclosure to protect your privacy, including encryption. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We cannot, therefore, warrant or ensure the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

If you are a registered user of AffSpy.com, your AffSpy.com account information is password protected so that only you have access to this personal information. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to anyone. AffSpy will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or unsolicited email. If you choose to share your user name and password or your personal information with third parties, you are responsible for all actions taken with your account and therefore you should review that third party’s privacy policy. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.

### How are children’s privacy protected?

Persons under the age of 18 (or 21, depending upon the age of majority in their jurisdiction) are not authorized to use the Site. Those persons are prohibited from submitting any personal information to us. 

### Additional Information

Any questions regarding this statement should be directed to privacy@affspy.com

This Policy, and the User Agreement, are the sole authorized statements of AffSpy’s practices with respect to the online collection of personally identifiable information and the usage of such information. Any summaries of this Policy generated by third party software or otherwise shall have no legal effect, are in no way binding upon AffSpy, shall not be relied upon in substitute for this Policy, and neither supersede nor modify this Policy.

AffSpy reserves the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from visitors, or that we otherwise collect concerning or in connection with the Site, to a third party in the event of a sale or other transfer of assets or of any portion of our business.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible.
